[
  {
    "question": "6 \u00d7 5",
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-11) \u00d7 (-1)",
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-9) \u00d7 (-4)",
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-1) \u00d7 (-2)",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3) \u00d7 (-6)",
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8) \u00d7 (-5)",
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6) \u00d7 (-8)",
    "answer": "48"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-2) \u00d7 (-14)",
    "answer": "28"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 \u00d7 12",
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-11) \u00d7 (-13)",
    "answer": "143"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-9) \u00d7 (-13)",
    "answer": "117"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-5) \u00d7 (-4)",
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 \u00d7 13",
    "answer": "130"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4) \u00d7 (-6)",
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 \u00d7 4",
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8) \u00d7 (-9)",
    "answer": "72"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-11) \u00d7 (-14)",
    "answer": "154"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8) \u00d7 (-1)",
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "11 \u00d7 13",
    "answer": "143"
  },
  {
    "question": "11 \u00d7 5",
    "answer": "55"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-1) \u00d7 (-7)",
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6) \u00d7 (-8)",
    "answer": "48"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 \u00d7 6",
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 \u00d7 8",
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6) \u00d7 (-10)",
    "answer": "60"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3) \u00d7 (-1)",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-9) \u00d7 (-13)",
    "answer": "117"
  },
  {
    "question": "13 \u00d7 6",
    "answer": "78"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-1) \u00d7 (-13)",
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7) \u00d7 (-3)",
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3) \u00d7 (-12)",
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-5) \u00d7 (-9)",
    "answer": "45"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-14) \u00d7 (-13)",
    "answer": "182"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3) \u00d7 (-11)",
    "answer": "33"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 \u00d7 7",
    "answer": "70"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 \u00d7 11",
    "answer": "77"
  },
  {
    "question": "15 \u00d7 10",
    "answer": "150"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 \u00d7 15",
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 \u00d7 11",
    "answer": "110"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 \u00d7 3",
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-2) \u00d7 (-12)",
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 \u00d7 13",
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-11) \u00d7 (-6)",
    "answer": "66"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-9) \u00d7 (-9)",
    "answer": "81"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 \u00d7 1",
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-12) \u00d7 (-12)",
    "answer": "144"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-2) \u00d7 (-13)",
    "answer": "26"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 \u00d7 12",
    "answer": "48"
  },
  {
    "question": "15 \u00d7 7",
    "answer": "105"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-10) \u00d7 (-11)",
    "answer": "110"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-2) \u00d7 4",
    "answer": "-8"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6) \u00d7 4",
    "answer": "-24"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 \u00d7 (-8)",
    "answer": "-32"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 \u00d7 (-14)",
    "answer": "-56"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 \u00d7 (-10)",
    "answer": "-10"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6) \u00d7 3",
    "answer": "-18"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 \u00d7 (-10)",
    "answer": "-70"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-11) \u00d7 14",
    "answer": "-154"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-15) \u00d7 4",
    "answer": "-60"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7) \u00d7 15",
    "answer": "-105"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3) \u00d7 3",
    "answer": "-9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7) \u00d7 8",
    "answer": "-56"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 \u00d7 (-8)",
    "answer": "-56"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 \u00d7 (-1)",
    "answer": "-10"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3) \u00d7 8",
    "answer": "-24"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 \u00d7 (-6)",
    "answer": "-60"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 \u00d7 (-12)",
    "answer": "-48"
  },
  {
    "question": "11 \u00d7 (-4)",
    "answer": "-44"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 \u00d7 (-9)",
    "answer": "-63"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 \u00d7 (-15)",
    "answer": "-30"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 \u00d7 (-8)",
    "answer": "-24"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 \u00d7 (-1)",
    "answer": "-1"
  },
  {
    "question": "12 \u00d7 (-2)",
    "answer": "-24"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 \u00d7 (-4)",
    "answer": "-8"
  },
  {
    "question": "12 \u00d7 (-10)",
    "answer": "-120"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-12) \u00d7 11",
    "answer": "-132"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8) \u00d7 5",
    "answer": "-40"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 \u00d7 (-4)",
    "answer": "-16"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 \u00d7 (-7)",
    "answer": "-49"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 \u00d7 (-1)",
    "answer": "-10"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-9) \u00d7 6",
    "answer": "-54"
  },
  {
    "question": "12 \u00d7 (-4)",
    "answer": "-48"
  },
  {
    "question": "12 \u00d7 (-8)",
    "answer": "-96"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 \u00d7 (-9)",
    "answer": "-36"
  },
  {
    "question": "15 \u00d7 (-1)",
    "answer": "-15"
  },
  {
    "question": "15 \u00d7 (-11)",
    "answer": "-165"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6) \u00d7 7",
    "answer": "-42"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6) \u00d7 10",
    "answer": "-60"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 \u00d7 (-11)",
    "answer": "-55"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-9) \u00d7 1",
    "answer": "-9"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 \u00d7 (-1)",
    "answer": "-2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4) \u00d7 11",
    "answer": "-44"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6) \u00d7 9",
    "answer": "-54"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 \u00d7 (-10)",
    "answer": "-100"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-9) \u00d7 12",
    "answer": "-108"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-10) \u00d7 12",
    "answer": "-120"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6) \u00d7 7",
    "answer": "-42"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8) \u00d7 12",
    "answer": "-96"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 \u00d7 (-9)",
    "answer": "-72"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-9) \u00d7 6",
    "answer": "-54"
  },
  {
    "question": "21 \u00f7 3",
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "96 \u00f7 8",
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-14) \u00f7 (-14)",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "72 \u00f7 9",
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "150 \u00f7 15",
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-14) \u00f7 (-14)",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "36 \u00f7 4",
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "210 \u00f7 15",
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-25) \u00f7 (-5)",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-48) \u00f7 (-4)",
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "13 \u00f7 1",
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "56 \u00f7 14",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-84) \u00f7 (-14)",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-24) \u00f7 (-12)",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "27 \u00f7 9",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-140) \u00f7 (-10)",
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "16 \u00f7 4",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "117 \u00f7 13",
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "16 \u00f7 4",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "130 \u00f7 10",
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "49 \u00f7 7",
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "168 \u00f7 12",
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "81 \u00f7 9",
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "24 \u00f7 8",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-15) \u00f7 (-5)",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-156) \u00f7 (-13)",
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "40 \u00f7 4",
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "60 \u00f7 15",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "45 \u00f7 3",
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "70 \u00f7 7",
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-42) \u00f7 (-7)",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "210 \u00f7 14",
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-20) \u00f7 (-10)",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-14) \u00f7 (-14)",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "66 \u00f7 11",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "14 \u00f7 1",
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-24) \u00f7 (-2)",
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8) \u00f7 (-8)",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "120 \u00f7 12",
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-140) \u00f7 (-10)",
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-49) \u00f7 (-7)",
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8) \u00f7 (-8)",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-22) \u00f7 (-2)",
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-9) \u00f7 (-3)",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-99) \u00f7 (-11)",
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-65) \u00f7 (-13)",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "55 \u00f7 11",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-48) \u00f7 (-12)",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-66) \u00f7 (-11)",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "36 \u00f7 4",
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-70) \u00f7 5",
    "answer": "-14"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-9) \u00f7 9",
    "answer": "-1"
  },
  {
    "question": "65 \u00f7 (-5)",
    "answer": "-13"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-112) \u00f7 8",
    "answer": "-14"
  },
  {
    "question": "80 \u00f7 (-8)",
    "answer": "-10"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-11) \u00f7 11",
    "answer": "-1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-98) \u00f7 14",
    "answer": "-7"
  },
  {
    "question": "40 \u00f7 (-8)",
    "answer": "-5"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-36) \u00f7 6",
    "answer": "-6"
  },
  {
    "question": "12 \u00f7 (-2)",
    "answer": "-6"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-40) \u00f7 4",
    "answer": "-10"
  },
  {
    "question": "36 \u00f7 (-9)",
    "answer": "-4"
  },
  {
    "question": "45 \u00f7 (-9)",
    "answer": "-5"
  },
  {
    "question": "117 \u00f7 (-13)",
    "answer": "-9"
  },
  {
    "question": "35 \u00f7 (-5)",
    "answer": "-7"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-84) \u00f7 6",
    "answer": "-14"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-90) \u00f7 10",
    "answer": "-9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-72) \u00f7 8",
    "answer": "-9"
  },
  {
    "question": "20 \u00f7 (-2)",
    "answer": "-10"
  },
  {
    "question": "72 \u00f7 (-8)",
    "answer": "-9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4) \u00f7 1",
    "answer": "-4"
  },
  {
    "question": "27 \u00f7 (-9)",
    "answer": "-3"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 \u00f7 (-3)",
    "answer": "-3"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 \u00f7 (-10)",
    "answer": "-1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-36) \u00f7 4",
    "answer": "-9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-195) \u00f7 15",
    "answer": "-13"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-48) \u00f7 6",
    "answer": "-8"
  },
  {
    "question": "60 \u00f7 (-6)",
    "answer": "-10"
  },
  {
    "question": "39 \u00f7 (-13)",
    "answer": "-3"
  },
  {
    "question": "88 \u00f7 (-8)",
    "answer": "-11"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-20) \u00f7 5",
    "answer": "-4"
  },
  {
    "question": "105 \u00f7 (-15)",
    "answer": "-7"
  },
  {
    "question": "22 \u00f7 (-2)",
    "answer": "-11"
  },
  {
    "question": "30 \u00f7 (-6)",
    "answer": "-5"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-56) \u00f7 8",
    "answer": "-7"
  },
  {
    "question": "24 \u00f7 (-2)",
    "answer": "-12"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-66) \u00f7 11",
    "answer": "-6"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-32) \u00f7 8",
    "answer": "-4"
  },
  {
    "question": "28 \u00f7 (-7)",
    "answer": "-4"
  },
  {
    "question": "72 \u00f7 (-6)",
    "answer": "-12"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-121) \u00f7 11",
    "answer": "-11"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-60) \u00f7 4",
    "answer": "-15"
  },
  {
    "question": "130 \u00f7 (-13)",
    "answer": "-10"
  },
  {
    "question": "16 \u00f7 (-8)",
    "answer": "-2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-11) \u00f7 11",
    "answer": "-1"
  },
  {
    "question": "91 \u00f7 (-7)",
    "answer": "-13"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-15) \u00f7 1",
    "answer": "-15"
  },
  {
    "question": "225 \u00f7 (-15)",
    "answer": "-15"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-22) \u00f7 11",
    "answer": "-2"
  },
  {
    "question": "36 \u00f7 (-6)",
    "answer": "-6"
  }
]